



# LU PEI-YUN CHUNG

# UX, UI & Product Designer based on New York

Working with consumer-focused product companies, SaaS, and B2B & B2C platforms, I have 3+ years of experience in UX, UI, and Visual Design. I am specializing in Human-Centered Design for websites and Apps.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Designer - Kronos Research Inc.**

Feb. 2019 - May. 2019. Taipei, Taiwan

Devised Career web design, development, photography. Directed visual design of Wallet MVP, UIs, prototypes.

# **UX Designer - Shopline Inc.**

Feb. 2017 - Apr. 2018. Taipei, Taiwan

Designed Merchant App, conducting the usability test. Delivered UIs of POS (Point of Sale) system. Revamped the Admin platform and storefront website. Compiled design guidelines and design principles. Designed customized websites on desktop and mobile.

#### **UI Desinger - AI Group Corp.**

Oct. 2016 - Dec. 2016. Taipei, Taiwan

Devised front-end website for the JUT art museum. Created the UIs of the JUT App for the office building.

#### **UI Designer - Techgiant Art Technology Inc.**

Feb. 2016 - Aug. 2016. Taipei, Taiwan

Devised product brand design, tangible UIs, and VUIs. Designed web design, graphic illustration, photography.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Pratt Institute, New York**

M.S. in Information Experience Design Sep 2019-Now GPA: 3.767/4.0; Pratt Institute Full-Scholarship Merit.

#### **National Kaohsiung Normal University, Taiwan**

M.F.A. in Visual Design Sep 2013-Jun 2016

Graduated Thesis Score: 92.0/100.0

Academic Awards: 1 First place and 1 Second place.

B.D. in Visual Design Sep 2009-Jun 2013

GPA: 3.91/4.0, 3 First places and 2 Second places. Vision-Get-Wild Award, HTC Packaging Silver Prize.

# **SELECT SKILLS**

Sketch, Figma, InVision, Adobe XD, Framer, Axure, Balsamiq, Zeplin, Origami Studio, User Flows Diagram.

User flows, Wireframes, Prototypes, Motion Uls, App, Web Design, WCAG, VUIs, Emotional Design.

Five Ws, Scenarios, Personas, User Journey Map, Competitors Analysis, Card Sort, Tree Test, Site Map.

Interviews, Observations, Questionnaires, Heuristic Evaluations, Design Critique, Usability Testing.

Social Media Analytics, SEO Audit Report, Google Data Studio, Google Analytics, Google Spreadsheets.